Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Bethlehem Steel Company, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Steel at the Crossroads: the American Steel Industry in the 1980s, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Messages From Senior Management, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Loop Course, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: A Look At Bethlehem, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Summary Evaluation of Performance and Promotability/Potential, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Fast Track to Management, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Bethlehem Steel's Loop Course, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: the National Shipbuilding Research Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: The national Shipbuilding Research Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: The National Shipbuilding Research Program, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Recollections, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Bethlehem Steel - Suggestion System, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: You Can Help Bethlehem Work Smarter In The 80s, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Bethlehem Steel's Take It To The Top Compaign Strategy and Analysis of Results, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Bottom Line, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Vol. II No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Conversations With Some Governors, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Bethlehem Review, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bethlehem Steel Impact Study, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Bethlehem Steel Impact Study, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Bethlehem Steel - Addresses, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Re-industrialization: Growing Focus of Business Government Relations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Remarks by Donald H. Trautlein, Chairman-Elect At Management Meeting, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Let Us Now Praise Famous Men, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Perspectives of An American Steel Producer, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Bethlehem Steel - Industrial Relations Dept., Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Performance Appraisal Workshop, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Conference Leadership Seminar, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Business Writing Seminar, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Office Supervisors' Seminar, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Bethlehem Wants Your Better Ideas Now, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Beyond Your Paycheck, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Computer A Management Tool Seminar, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Middle Management Seminar, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Communications Improvement Workshop, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Bethlehem Steel, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Butte Knitting Mills, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Contact, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Contact, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Contact, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Contact, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bethlehem Steel-History, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Brief History, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: History of Steelmaking, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Bethlehem Steel - Public Affairs Dept., Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Is "Big Business" Bad Business?, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Steel Industry Myths and Facts, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: CAP Talk -- Essentiality, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Loop Course, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Steel Scene, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Big Business Day April 17, 1980, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Big Business Day, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Big Business Day Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Bituminous Coal Operators Assoc., Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Stability in the Coal Industry, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Blue Cross Assoc., Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A monthly publication for employees of BCBSA, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A monthly publication for employees of BCBSA, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Human Resources Newsletter, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    August 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Questions and Answers About The bLue Cross and Blue Shield Organization, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Organization Services, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: TO: All Human Resources Officers, Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Chief Plan Executives - All Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Human Resources Training and Development Catalog, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Administrative Handbook, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Boeing Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: C-1132 (C-1114 Updated), Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Professional Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Seattle the nation's most beautiful city, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Boeing and You, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1990, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Boeing Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Company Profile, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: First Family Commercial Jet Airplanes, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Tuition Reimbursement Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Boise Cascade, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Insight, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Insight, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: A Profile, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: A Presentation to the New York Society of Security Analysis, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: 1987 Annual Reports, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: 1987 Statistical Information, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Annual Meeting of Shareholders, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Boise Cascade, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Forests, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Papermaking at Boise Cascade Paper Group, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: We Know Where We're Growing, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: A Profile, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Directions for Boise Cascade, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Insight, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    August 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Statistical Information, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: U.S. Salaried Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Booz-Allen, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Information Outline For Prospective Staff, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Borden Co., Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Administrative Headquarters Employees Guide, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Borden News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Third Quarter. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: BordeNews, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Second Quarter. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: BordeNews, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    First Quarter. Item is in English.
- Borders, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Union Awareness Training For Borders Managers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Boston & Maine Railroad, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet: STIP Contract with the Boston and Maine Railroad, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Bristol-Meyers Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Timeline, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Bristol-Myers New York, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Bristol-Myers New York, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Medical Department To Your Health, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: 1985 Report Equal Opportunity at Bristol-Myers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Your Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Non-exempt Employee Referral Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: The Bristol-Myers Career Education Awards Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Equal Employment Opportunity Guide, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: child Care Information, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: The Bristol-Myers Company Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Bristol-Myers NY, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Dun's Business Month, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Comprehensive Health Care Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Non-exempt Performance Appraisal & Salary Review, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Exempt Performance Appraisal and Salary Review, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Labor Documents, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Bristol-Myers Squibb Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Equal Opportunity At Bristol-Myers Squibb Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
    1990 Report. Item is in English.
- Brookings Institution, Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Is There Enough Manpower?, Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Brown and Williamson Tobacco Corp., Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Policy & Procedures Statement Employees Relocated to Macon, Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Burlington Industries, Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Burlington Industries Salaried Employees' Handbook, Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Performance Review Exempt, Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Performance Review Non-exempt, Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Fact Sheet: Apprenticeship at Burlington Northern Railroad, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet: Apprenticeship at Burlington Northern Railroad, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Burroughs Corporation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Transborder Data Flow and the New Protectionism, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Remarks by W. Michael Blumenthal, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Remarks By W. Michael Blumenthal, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Burroughs Cooperatiuve Education Program, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Performance Planning and Evaluation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Personnel Policies & Practices Manual, Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Burroughs Corporation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: After Hours Philadelphia, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Vol. 2, No. 1 Winter. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Vol. 1, No. 1 Fall. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Vol. 2, No. 2 Spring. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Vol. 2, No. 3 Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Vol. 2, No. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Info, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Info, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Burroughs People, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Facts: Burroughs Corporation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Info, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: In Focus, Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Jan/Feb. Item is in English.
- CNA Insurance Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: CAN Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: CAN Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: CAN Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: CAN Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
    February/March. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: CNA Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
    May/ June. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: CNA Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: CNA Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: CNA Inside, Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
- CNA Insurance Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Pacer Reports, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Viewpoint, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    third Quarter. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Viewpoint, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Fourth Quarter. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Personnel Manual, Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
- CNA Insurance Company "Inside", Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Inside CNA, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Inside CNA, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Dec/ Jan. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Inside CNA, Publication (Box 8, Folder 22)
    July/Aug. Item is in English.
- CSX Corporation, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Leadership in Transportation Energy Technology Properties, Publication (Box 8, Folder 23)
- California Dept. of Industrial Relations News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    July 6, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    March 28, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    September 19, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    December 10, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    January 21, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    January 8, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 24)
    December 6, 1982. Item is in English.
- California - Industrial Welfare Commission, Publication (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: What California has done to Protect Women Workers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 25)
- California Institute of Technology, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Working at CALTECH, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Opportunities for Professional & Personal Development, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Caltech HMO/Prepaid Health Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Student Health Center Services and Student Health Insurance Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Summary Plan Descriptions for the CALTECH Insurance Plans, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Comparison of Health Plan Benefits, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Group Health Insurance Economy 500 Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Group Health Insurance Base Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Summar of life Insurance Coverage, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: Group Long Term Disability Insurance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 11: Group Personal Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: Group Dental Plan, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 14: Caltech, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 15: Position Description Questionnaire, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: The California Tech, Publication (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Friday Nov 14. Item is in English.
- California, University of, Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Summary of Your Benefits at the University of California, Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Your Benefits from the University's Retirement Plan and Social Security, Publication (Box 8, Folder 27)
- California Workers' Compensation Institute, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.94-10. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.94-14. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.94-16. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.94-17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-4. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-5. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-6. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-7. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-8. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-9. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-10. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-11. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-12. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-13. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-14. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-15. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-16. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-17. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-18. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-19. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-20. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-21. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.95-22. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.96-3. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.96-4. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 28)
    no.96-5. Item is in English.
- Campbell Soup Company, Publication (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Canada Dry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Mid-year Performance Update, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Performance Appraisal - Non Exempt, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Performance & Development Review, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Medical-Dental Claim Kit, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your Cadbury Schweppes Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Performance Appraisal Program, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Performance Appraisal Program, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Office and Laboratory Personnel. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Business Reply Mail, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Safety Sentinel, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Savings Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Medical, Life, Disability, and Accident Programs, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Pension Plan For salaried Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Bulletin, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Skills Questionnaire, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Principles of Business Conduct, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Training and Professional Development, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Standard Oil Engineered Materials Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Standard Oil Exempt Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: The Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Guidelines for the Carborundum Salaried Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Fiberfax, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Issue 19 September. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Guidelines at-a Glance, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: The Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Carrier Corporation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How We Benefit You, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Careers at Carrier, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: the Two Faces of Janus, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Professional Objectives and Assessment, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Professional Self-evaluation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Building For Our Second Century, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Building For Our Second Century, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Employement Opprotunities in Our Second Century, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: American Heritage, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Carrier World, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Carrier Oil Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Carter Oil Company, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Life Insurance and Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Benefits Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Caterpillar, Inc., Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Benefit Plans and Salary Practices for Caterpillar Salaried Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Benefit Plans and Salary Practices for Caterpillar Salaried Nonexempt Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Benefit Plans for Solar Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Benefit Plans Caterpillar Salaried Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Product Line, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: NIU Commencement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Twin Cities Society of Security Analysts, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Making Caterpillar Competitive, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Caterpillar Story, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Caterpillar World Special Historical Edition, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Salary Administration System, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: A Code of Worldwide Business Conduct and Operating Principles, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Folks, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    February 19. Item is in English.
- Caterpillar, Inc., Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Caterpillar World, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Caterpillar World, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Caterpillar, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Pursuing Excellence, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Caterpillar Inc. - House Organs, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Benefit Program Highlights, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Performance Review Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Non-exempt performance review, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Personal Growth Plan, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Exempt Employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ideas and Challenges, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)